

Summary

Hello, I'm Ashley O'Connor, a 29-yearold professional residing in Paynesville, Victoria. I am a dedicated husband and father to a wonderful daughter. I have a decade of diverse expertise, I excelled as a punctual Truck Driver at Grinter Transport, showcasing strong time management and navigational skills, ensuring efficient deliveries and upholding safety measures. At Reece Group, I provided exceptional customer service, managed transactions, and maintained an organised workspace, consistently surpassing targets. In my own time, I enjoy snowsports, watersports and playing video games.



0400021818



ashoconnor94@gmail.com



Paynesville, Victoria, Australia



linkedin.com/in/ash-oconnor/

Skills

- Time Management
- Problem-solving
- Attention to Detail
- Team Collaboration
- Customer Service
- Organisational Skills
- High Computer Literacy
- Safety Focus

ASHLEY O'CONNOR

Mature Age Student

Experience

Truck Driver Grinter Transport. Bairnsdale. 2021 - 2023

- Reliable and punctual driver with strong time management skills, consistently meeting delivery deadlines.
- Skilled in performing routine vehicle maintenance, ensuring safety, and minimising downtime.

Counter Staff Reece Group. Bairnsdale. 2012 - 2021

- Provided exceptional customer service to ensure satisfaction and resolve inquiries.
- · Handles cash transactions accurately and efficiently.
- Maintained a clean and organised workspace, ensuring a professional and inviting environment.
- Collaborated with team members to support overall store operations and meet performance targets.

Education

RMIT University

BACHELOR OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY RMIT UNIVERSITY. ONLINE. MAY 2021 - FEB 2023

Unfortunately, due to the course transitioning into techout mode, I was unable to complete this degree as a part-time student at RMIT. However, I will be completing the degree at another institution.

Subjects completed during the degree:

- Introduction to Information Technology: High Distinction (HD)
- Introduction to Programming: High Distinction (HD)
- Introduction to Computer Systems: Distinction (DI)
- Building IT Systems: High Distinction (HD)
- Database Concepts: Distinction (DI)
- User-centered Design: Distinction (DI)
- Web Programming: High Distinction (HD)